This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Bucky D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum-gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
From this sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cover path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Luffy discovered that his brother Ace was captured by the Navy and now faces execution.
With the help of the Snake Princess,
Luffy snuck aboard a Navy ship bound for the prison known as Impel Town.
The Friends' Whereabouts, the science of weather and the mechanical island!
If you were to take a trip, where would you want to go?
Zoro!
Brook, no!
Russo!
Musso!
Sanji!
Frankie!
Gnami!
Shufu-Bard!
Luffy!
Luffy?
It was a dream.
You were screaming. It sounded like it was awful.
I lost all my friends a second time.
I see.
Surely there's something I can say to raise his spirits.
Hey, Luffy.
You don't need to worry.
Right now you have to put all of your focus into saving your brother.
Have faith that your friends can look after themselves.
You trust them, right?
Yeah, of course.
Now remember, even though you were separated from your crew, you have never been alone.
I'm right here to comfort you if you need me.
You mean that, don't you?
Hancock, I've been so foolish.
All this time, I was with an angel and had no idea.
Luffy.
Hancock.
Clearly, that's exactly what he would say.
No, we can't.
Oh, hey, Hammock, what are you doing?
Not long ago.
Only a few days before, in fact.
Goodness, what was that noise?
Be careful now.
Hmm.
Well, this is new.
Are you finally awake?
Ah!
What is this?
Who the heck are you?
Where am I?
Calm down. You're in my house.
I dragged you in here while you...
You did what to me?
Oh, I'm scared.
Your body's still healing, so you shouldn't move around too much.
And you won't get far in this weather.
Just stay back!
I don't care what shape my body's in.
I'm getting out of your creepy shack.
My crewmates need me.
I've got to get back to them.
Back off!
Please forgive me.
I can't help wanting to help you.
I said back off, you freak!
I can't help you.
I'll be glad you did this anyway.
I'll be happy.
Hey, hi, hi, hi, hi.
How am I doing this, how am I doing it?
You're way right, everything.
Hey there.
I'm out here in my 중요한 range.
Let's go.
I'm out there in my room.
Just wonder if you remember...
how
Hey, hey hey hey, hey hey, hey hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, there, young lady.
Young lady who came plummeting out of the sky?
Yeah, I heard you. What?
Do you think you've calmed down a little now?
No more inclinations toward violence?
Yeah.
This is good.
Oh, it's nothing special, really.
You slept for two days after you crashed,
so I'm sure anything would taste amazing right now.
Wait, I was out for two days?
You really must have been through quite the ordeal, haven't you?
Ta-da!
This may look like ordinary rope,
but they are, in fact, tightly wound wind knots.
If I untie one, it creates a gentle breeze,
but if I untie two, a strong gust will blow,
and if I untie three, it becomes a gale!
What'd you do that for?
I'm sorry, I just thought it might cheer you up, that's all.
Oh, yeah, I'm real cheery now. I'm out of here.
Don't be crazy, young lady.
You'll get yourself killed out there.
This isn't so bad.
I can handle this.
I know those clouds.
We're in the path of a huge cyclone.
Oh, no, just look at you.
You've got mud all over.
Why don't you come in and take a shower?
You get yourself clean, and I'll wash and dry your clothes for you.
Listen up, old man.
Yes, young lady?
That isn't any ordinary rainstorm.
There's a cyclone coming, a huge one that'll barrel right through us.
Did you say something?
I'm trying to tell you we're in trouble!
We're right in the path of a gigantic storm!
Oh, yes, it's coming this way.
Hopefully with some more pleasant company.
Jeez.
Dumb old coot.
Well, I've already warned him once.
What?
Rain clouds?
Just turn the wheel, and hot water will come out.
Turn the wheel?
They're raining hot water?
How is this possible?
Is the water temperature okay?
If you push the wheel, it'll blow hot air.
I made tea while you bathed.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, that's nice.
Wait, why are we so calm?
That giant storm is going to wreck this place!
Unlike you, I'm too young to die!
Oh, please don't start throwing objects at me!
There's really nothing we can do?
Oh, yes.
It's time.
I'll be back before you know it.
You just stay inside and wait here.
Okay, young lady?
What?
Hey, no!
Wait!
How is he able to walk so easily in this weather?
There it is!
Now, cool bulb!
Heat bulb!
Cool bulb!
Here we go! Cyclone Burst!
No!
Well, damn!
Hey there, I'm talking to you, young lady!
you don't say okay what's up well now i only showed it to you the one time and you're using
the wind knot like a pro you're quite impressive nothing to it anyway looks like it's time for me
to go wow this is a surprise are those where are we
this is a small sky island called with area we conduct studies of the weather here what this is
a sky island a cyclone looked like it had the possibility to be a rather intriguing specimen
but it just suddenly up and disappeared on us now i wonder how that could have happened
and so nami found herself on a small island in the sky will she ever be able to find her way back to
her friends
the storm is only getting worse why don't we take a break somewhere kitten okay
is something wrong toroimo
it's huge get behind me
hold on wait what are you doing
what he's a human
this is terrible what are we gonna do um excuse me are you all right sir my dog he thought you were
something we're hunting
yeah no biggie
it's like this guy doesn't even care
no harm done then i bet you're relieved toroimo
there is one problem though where the heck am i and how did i get here
it's cold damn don't you have the sun here
frankie oh no he's only wearing underwear and all the snow did bandits do your pants
why don't you put on this fur pelt
whoa a fur pelt no thanks i'm trying to maintain a style here
that'd cram my reputation as a freak
oh i gotta move man like this wow come on follow my lead
shake your hips to the right
right hand to the waist
and then stick out your left hand
now slide and reverse
right left right left right left right left
now repeat after me guys one two one two right left right left right left right left
one two one two one two right left right left right left right left
wow one two one two
super that's how it's done
Crap! I'm still freezing!
Where the hell is this place?
What? You don't know where you are?
Why would I know something like that?
This is the Futureland Baltimore, which is located on Mechanical Island.
It's known as the birthplace of the genius.
The what now?
The genius.
The... the who?
Mr. Oh, my.
He really should have taken the belt.
We better get him to the hospital, Kevin.
Yeah.
We better get him to the school.
On the next lap.
Well, he's definitely a cyborg.
I can't believe he runs on cola.
What should we do?
We don't have any sodas to refuel him.
There's no time to lose.
We need to begin.
Right.
Hey, mister!
You seem different.
Hello.
You're the young lad from earlier, correct?
I do hope I haven't kept you waiting for too long.
Yeah, you're definitely different.
What did they do to you?
Well, it seems that cola is hard to come by here,
so they brewed up some fine hot tea instead.
Dodge healing, to be precise.
Hot tea?
The aroma and flavor are truly super.
Lovely.
There's really nothing quite so relaxing.
Okay, if you say so.
I'm sorry.
Where are my manners?
Enjoy.
Careful.
It's hot.
No!
This is weird!
It's all wrong!
Hey, mister!
You're not funny now.
I liked you more the way you were.
Oh?
Is that so?
What was I like before, pray tell?
You were like this.
Hmm?
Super!
You know, lad, that's just a tad and bench.
We need to get you some color right away!
And so Frankie became a gentleman on Mechanical Island.
Will he ever be a super freak again?
And what does fate have in store for the rest of the straw hats
scattered around the globe?
Yeah.
Shopper awakens on a faraway island only to be attacked by giant birds and natives
hungry for a reindeer dinner.
Meanwhile, Sanji finds himself in a peach-colored paradise.
The inhabitants seem harmless enough,
but is Sanji walking into a trap?
On the next One Piece, The Friend's Whereabouts,
an island of giant birds and a pink paradise.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!